{
    "id": "8c73d3b3e3e642e4b51046a40787a1ee",
    "title": "Conditional Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I had a penny, I ………………… some peanuts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can buy",
                "could buy",
                "could have bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33bd3d3cc820450f82ecbcd4639b4353"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ………………… her address, I could have a written to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5d9a3d98952f4ba1b4c3b46343be1915"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. if he had been more careful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may not fall",
                "might not fall",
                "might not have fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b01d9dcdc55a4b388c3a38b47c9d4c7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… . you if I had enough money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will help",
                "would help",
                "would have helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a0132a7a97f4e48a78fe74f29670068"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were in your position, I …………………….. such a disgraceful act.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not commit",
                "would not commit",
                "would not have committed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bf6a26d96b1f4c89b8705603dee9d693"
        },
        {
            "question": "What would you do if you ………………….. the first prize in a bumper draw?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "got",
                "had gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eefb97b6e4004ec0aa51fa63876a3aac"
        },
        {
            "question": "There might have been a great flood, if the rains …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not stop",
                "had not stopped",
                "would not stop"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1b46c61ad014d4aa4a37178578b9611"
        },
        {
            "question": "Had the driver been alert, the accident ………………….............",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could be averted",
                "can be averted",
                "could have been averted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "760fde13844b495992c0e99b303a97bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would not accept the offer, if I ……………………… you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c299f603c1b24d7cbeeac54373c67cf2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you were a little more careful, you ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would not be cheated",
                "will not be cheated",
                "would not have been cheated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98da2ee1eb47413db31d342f194b2cc0"
        }
    ]
}